<quotes>

    <!-- RICHARD DAWKINS QUOTES -->
    <quote>
        <content>The fact that life evolved out of nearly nothing, some 10 billion years after the universe evolved out of literally nothing, is a fact so staggering that I would be mad to attempt words to do it justice.</content>
        <author>RICHARD_DAWKINS</author>
        <tags>Biology,Evolution,Science</tags>
    </quote>

    <quote>
        <content>Let us try to teach generosity and altruism, because we are born selfish. Let us understand what our own selfish genes are up to, because we may then at least have a chance to upset their designs, something that no other species has ever aspired to do</content>
        <author>RICHARD_DAWKINS</author>
        <tags>Morality,Biology,Genetics</tags>
    </quote>

     <quote>
        <content>An atheist is just somebody who feels about Yahweh the way any decent Christian feels about Thor or Baal or the golden calf. As has been said before, we are all atheists about most of the gods that humanity has ever believed in. Some of us just go one god further. </content>
        <author>RICHARD_DAWKINS</author>
        <tags>Atheism,Philosophy,Religion</tags>
    </quote>

    <!-- SAM HARRIS QUOTES -->
    <quote>
        <content>Death is, in some ways, unacceptable. It’s just an astonishing fact of our being here that we die; but I think worse than that is if we live long enough, we lose everyone we love in this world. I mean people die and disappear, and we’re left with this stark mystery: just the sheer not knowing of what happened to them.</content>
        <author>SAM_HARRIS</author>
        <tags>Philosophy,Spirituality</tags>
    </quote>

    <quote>
        <content>As a general matter, I believe we should be very slow to make conclusions about the nature of the cosmos based upon inner experience – no matter how profound these experiences seem.</content>
        <author>SAM_HARRIS</author>
        <tags>Philosophy,Spirituality</tags>
    </quote>

     <quote>
        <content>The problem with faith, is that it really is a conversation stopper. Faith is a declaration of immunity to the powers of conversation. It is a reason, why you do not have to give reasons, for what you believe.</content>
        <author>SAM_HARRIS</author>
        <tags>Philosophy,Religion,Atheism</tags>
    </quote>

    <!-- CHRISTOPHER HITCHENS QUOTES -->
    <quote>
        <content>The essence of the independent mind lies not in what it thinks, but in how it thinks.</content>
        <author>CHRISTOPHER_HITCHENS</author>
        <tags>Philosophy,Opinion</tags>
    </quote>

    <quote>
        <content>Faith is the surrender of the mind; it's the surrender of reason, it's the surrender of the only thing that makes us different from other mammals.</content>
        <author>CHRISTOPHER_HITCHENS</author>
        <tags>Philosophy,Religion,Atheism</tags>
    </quote>

     <quote>
        <content>My challenge is really to say, 'Can you name me a moral action or a statement that has been made by a believer that couldn't have been made by a non-believer?'</content>
        <author>CHRISTOPHER_HITCHENS</author>
        <tags>Philosophy,Atheism,Religion,Morality</tags>
    </quote>
    
    <!-- DANIEL DENNETT QUOTES -->
    <quote>
        <content>We really have to think of reasoning the way we think of romance, it takes two to tango. There has to be a communication.</content>
        <author>DANIEL_DENNETT</author>
        <tags>Philosophy,Reason</tags>
    </quote>

    <quote>
        <content>We live in a world that is subjectively open. And we are designed by evolution to be "informavores," epistemically hungry seekers of information, in an endless quest to improve our purchase on the world.</content>
        <author>DANIEL_DENNETT</author>
        <tags>Biology,Evolution,Science</tags>
    </quote>

     <quote>
        <content>Or you can thank God — but the very idea of repaying God is ludicrous. What could an omniscient, omnipotent Being (the Man Who has Everything?) do with any paltry repayments from you?</content>
        <author>DANIEL_DENNETT</author>
        <tags>Philosophy,Religion,Atheism,Spirituality</tags>
    </quote>

</quotes>